{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "78 + 28",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 68",
      "answer": 109,
      "test": {
        "q": "name of the 2020 USA president",
        "a": "???"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 80",
      "answer": 166
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 32",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 17",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 5",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 2",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 13",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 82",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 94",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 23",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 87",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 95",
      "answer": 177
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 70",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 57",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 33",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 40",
      "answer": 130
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 40",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 96",
      "answer": 158
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 72",
      "answer": 168
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 56",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 83",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 89",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 86",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 63",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 76",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 47",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 71",
      "answer": 144
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 25",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 29",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 5",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 67",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 57",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 72",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 40",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 15",
      "answer": 43
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 11",
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 47",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 40",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 36",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 43",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 84",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 79",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 67",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 13",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 5",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 24",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 27",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 92",
      "answer": 187
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 91",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 71",
      "answer": 171
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 16",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 20",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 55",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 37",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 72",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 94",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 83",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 48",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 14",
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 97",
      "answer": 177
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 90",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 31",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 66",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 98",
      "answer": 177
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 23",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 3",
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 21",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 24",
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 97",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 12",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 83",
      "answer": 181
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 53",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 77",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 3",
      "answer": 22
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 58",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 94",
      "answer": 187
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 24",
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 58",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 51",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 59",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 16",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 59",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 67",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 99",
      "answer": 184
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 12",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 30",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 38",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 75",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 38",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 5",
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 1",
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 28",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 86",
      "answer": 185
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 57",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 44",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 71",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 88",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 69",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 41",
      "answer": 51
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 11,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1000,
      "to": 1100
    }
  }
}